smartcarofamerica.com 2008-03-07

# Smart Car of America - The leading smart fortwo news and information portal - Privacy Policy for SmartCar Of America.com

Privacy Policy for SmartCar Of America.com   
  
> > Privacy for Web Visitors. 

One can visit our Web site with complete privacy. A Web site visitor can chose to provide customer-specific information by ordering a product or service, sending us e-mail or registering on a company Web site. Any information provided by a Web site visitor is held strictly confidential within the family of SmartCar Of America companies or its authorized agent and will not be sold to any other organization or business. 

Privacy for Internet Service Subscribers.  
SmartCar Of America's affiliated Internet companies and services - collect information from Internet subscribers or users as necessary to provide a better Internet experience. For example, Web servers automatically recognize an Internet user's domain name (such as .com, .edu, etc.), the Web page from which a visitor enters our site and how much time a visitor spends on a Web page. This information is used - to improve our Internet services and provide better useabilty to our customers. 

Types of Customer Information.  
On some Web pages users can order products, make requests or register to receive information. Such customer-specific information will be used to fulfill the specific request or purpose for which it was provided. In addition, such voluntarily provided information may be occasionally used to offer products and services that may be of interest. Internet users have a choice to "opt out" if they prefer not to receive this type of information. 

Privacy of Online Personal Information.  
No personal information obtained online is released outside of the family of SmartCar Of America companies or its authorized agent, except with the customer's permission, as required by law, for safety reasons, or to survey customer satisfaction, under nondisclosure protection. We use the information provided when placing an order to complete that order. We do not share that information with outside parties except as necessary to fulfill the online order (e.g., providing the "ship to" address to our shipper.) We may also use that information to offer other products or services of interest. We do not sell customer information to any outside party. 

Use of Customer Information.  
Information collected online, especially from those who place an order online, may be used within the SmartCar Of America family of companies or by an authorized agent to inform the user about services and products of potential interest. Customers might be contacted by telephone, direct mail or e-mail to keep them up-to-date on new products and services offered by SmartCar Of America's family of companies or an authorized agent. Web visitors or Internet service subscribers who do not want to hear about new products or services can opt out of any potential use of customer information. 

Access by Children.  
SmartCar Of America Web sites are not structured to attract children. SmartCar Of America's affiliated companies believe there is information on its Web sites, which is inappropriate for viewing by children. Ordering online products and services from SmartCar Of America's affiliated companies is limited to adults. 

Other Web Sites.  
The Web sites of SmartCar Of America and its family of companies may contain links to other Web sites. We are not responsible for the content or privacy policies of other sites. 

Data Security.  
To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy and ensure only appropriate use of information, appropriate physical, electronic and managerial safeguards have been established to secure the information collected online. 

Correction of Information.  
To request access to customer-specific information or to correct any inaccuracies, email [customersevice@smartcarofamerica.com.](mailto:customersevice@smartcarofamerica.com.)

Updates.  
To improve the service SmartCar Of America and its affiliated companies offer, the information obtained about Web users may be revised in the future. This privacy statement will be updated to reflect any future developments in Internet business practices. Effective 5/02 

>
